

ASHLEY WINNOP

full stack designer & developer

CONTACT

**** 208.691.5996

✓ arwinnop@gmail.com

www.ashleywinnop.com

github.com/alchemistAshley

LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

HTML
CSS (Bootstrap & Ulkit)
Styled-Components
Javascript
jQuery
TypeScript
Express
Handlebars
Passport
Sequelize
Mongoose
React
Angular

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

PHP (Laravel)

Node.js
Git (Github, Gitlab)
MySQL
MongoDB
Firebase
Visual Studio Code
Android Studio
IntelliJ
Postman
Adobe CC (Illustrator, InDesign,
Photoshop, Animate)
OS (Linux, Mac, Windows)

ABOUT

Full stack designer & developer passionate about creating functional art. Most inspired when coming up with a thoughtful solution to a challenging problem. Focused on writing clean, concise, and efficient code to build elegant, responsive user interfaces and enjoyable user experiences.

EXPERIENCE

STUDENT

University of Denver | April 2018 - July 2018

- Acquired front-end and back-end web development experience
- Utilized object-oriented programming languages and frameworks to create full-stack web applications

CO-FOUNDER & CREATIVE DIRECTOR

Legend Social Inc. | February 2017 - November 2017

- Created product vision & strategies
- Designed app graphics, company logo & website
- Built user interface with best user experience in mind

VOLUNTEER ENGAGEMENT COORDINATOR

Spokane County United Way | February 2016 - February 2017

- Administered volunteer management database
- Established a new youth volunteer incentive program
- Produced social media marketing materials & graphics

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT CODING BOOTCAMP

University of Denver Denver, Colorado | 2018

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Attention to Detail
Empathy
Problem Solving
Philomath

INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS FRENCH | TEFL CERTIFICATE

University of Central Florida Orlando, Florida | 2015

INTERESTS

Baking Cooking Music Reading Yoga